pixafy.com 2016-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Pixafy : Pixafy

### GENERAL

Pixafy Services, LLC (Pixafy) recognizes that our clients’ privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when clients use Pixafy’s services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information.

Pixafy clients’ information, which includes personal contact information and server data, is treated with strict confidentiality and will not be shared except in the limited circumstances outlined in this policy. Pixafy adheres to the U.S.-EU and U.S. -Swiss Safe Harbor Framework and the principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement. Pixafy regularly reviews its compliance with this framework and these principles.

Pixafy collects cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and is used only internally to improve the content we provide to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. If you choose to communicate to us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless required to do so by law or in circumstances outlined in this policy.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

Users may voluntarily provide Pixafy with their contact information including, but not limited to, email address, name, telephone number, address, zip code and other personally identifiable information. This information will be used by Pixafy to respond to user inquiries and provide follow up communications. For example, users may voluntarily submit contact information to Pixafy in connection with: placing product orders, sending emails to Pixafy, engaging in phone conversations, help desk tickets or marketing promotions. Users may opt-out, modify or delete their personal information by sending an email to info@pixafy.com, by “unsubscribing” within the www.pixafy.com interface, or by using the unsubscribe link contained within our email communications.

### INFORMATION SHARING

Pixafy only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Pixafy in the following limited circumstances:

1\. With your consent: We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

2\. For legal, protective or enforcement purposes: We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to:

satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;  
enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations of those Terms;  
detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or  
protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Pixafy, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
Per our agreement with the Internet Corporation of Assigned Names and Numbers (ICANN), we must add valid contact information to the Whois directory for each domain name and IP you register. It is possible to purchase Private Registration by requesting it from your salesperson at the time of your order. By using private registration you can hide your personal contact information and display proxy information instead. Private Registration is available for many domain name extensions. However, some registries do not allow it.

### WHEN YOU VISIT OUR SITE

Pixafy may gather information from your web visit (as detailed below) to be analyzed in connection with providing the best products and services for our clients. This information helps us to customize products and content as well as developing an efficient browsing experience with regard to our site and the products/information contained therein. Thus, we may track visitor IP addresses as well as utilize unique alphanumeric identifiers (as detailed below) and web beacons (as detailed below) upon visits. This helps diagnose problems with our servers, administer our Websites, recognize details of visits (including, but not limited to, unique visits and sources of visits), tailor web content to users, avoid users viewing repeat content, improve our web structure and to analyze the effectiveness of our content. Specifically excluded is the collection of personal information from visitors so long as it does not pertain to public computer details or information disclosed by users via live and email communication with our site.

Pixafy users are informed that we may archive information provided to us via live communication (calls, visits, any other real-time communication) as well as information submitted in writing (web forms, order processing, email) to verify customer identities and provide our users with the best possible product as well as the most efficient user experience possible. Telephone calls may also be recorded for training purposes. Information submitted via the above methods may be combined with statistics gathered from web visits to measure interest in or develop our web pages and marketing plans, customize the content you view on your web visits based on your activity on past visits, develop generalized customer/consumer profiles, and administer our website.

What is a “visit”? There are a number of methods of approach to Pixafy’s website that are considered a “visit.” These include utilizing a web browser that delivers you to www.pixafy.com or any other site for which the previous URL’s can be considered a “root” to, as well as any other sites that are owned by, Pixafy. This may also include viewing an email that has content delivered from one of our servers (or a third party web server), or by viewing an advertisement displayed on a third party website that has content delivered by one of our web servers.

When web visits occur, our server may log the time/duration of your visit as well as the pages you visited and the time/duration spent on them. If your arrival results from a sponsored link, paid advertisement or paid search result, statistics may be gathered from your visit. In any other event, information may also be gathered based on where your visit originated as well as public computer data, visible to the analysis in place.

What is an “alphanumeric identifier”?During your visit, a unique alphanumeric identifier may be placed on your hard drive to help us identify visitors for customization and analysis. These identifiers may also be known as “cookies” and cannot be executed as code, used to deliver a virus, be identifiable to other servers, nor can any personal information be gathered by them. Pixafy utilizes this method solely for the aggregation of statistics used to enhance the product we offer users. If you do not want these identifiers placed upon your visit, cookies can be disabled in your web browser in the security settings that control them. It is important to note, however, that disabling cookies may hinder your ability to utilize our website at its intended performance level or to execute some functions contained in which cookies are required for security purposes.

What is a “web beacon”? A web beacon is a small graphic that may be embedded into Pixafy advertisements, emails or web pages. This small graphic will result in your web browser requesting the beacon from a web server. This request results in your web browser acquiring a unique identifier that may track visitor movement on the website utilizing the web beacon. Pixafy uses web beacons to provide customized offers and gain usage statistics that help tailor the most desired viewing experience for the majority of our visitors. Other than raw usage statistics, no personal information is gleaned by Pixafy’s web beacons.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Pixafy may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Pixafy’s sole discretion. Pixafy encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you have additional questions, please contact us any time. Or write to us at [info@pixafy.com](mailto:info@pixafy.com)
